Finding Aid for the Office of the Chancellor. Administrative files of Franklin D. Murphy. UARC.0401
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Final Report of the Task Force on Communications., 1969 Sep. (Box 105)
  Index code 171.
- Ombudsman., 1969-1970. (Box 105)
- Student Conduct/Student Discipline., 1969-1970. (Box 105)
- University Policies Commission (UPC), 1969-1970. (Box 105)
- Final Report of the Task Force on Education Reform., 1969 Sep. (Box 106)
- Final Report of the Task Force on War-Related Activities and ROTC., 1969 Sep. (Box 106)
- Final Report of the Task Force on Causes and Implications of Violence on University Campus., 1969 Sep. (Box 106)
- Bureau of Business and Economic Research., 1966-1968. (Box 107)
  Index code 172.
- Cancer Research Institute., 1965. (Box 107)
  Index code 174.
- Chairs., 1967-1969. (Box 107)
  Index code 175.
- Chamber of Commerce., 1968. (Box 107)
  Index code 185.
- Chancellor's Calendar., 1962-1964. (Box 107)
  Index code 186.
- Chancellor's Individual or Personal Membership in and Sponsorhop of Organizations., 1962-1970. (Box 107)
  Index code 193.
- Consultants., 1957-1970. (Box 107)
  Index codes 177.
- Estates., 1966. (Box 107)
  Index code 178.
- Food Services. Associated Students., 1970. (Box 107)
  Index codes 176.
- Grading., 1966-1968. (Box 107)
  Index code 180.
- Humanities., 1967-1969. (Box 107)
  Index code 184.
- Invitations to Affairs., 1965-1970. (Box 107)
  Index code 187.
- Invitations to Speak., 1969. (Box 107)
  Index code 188.
- Junior Colleges., 1968-1970. (Box 107)
  Index code 179.
- Rehabilitation Center., 1965-1970. (Box 107)
  Index code 173.
- REQ., 1968. (Box 107)
  Index code 190R.
- Security Studies Project., 1966-1969. (Box 107)
  Index code 182.
- Speeches, Statements and Articles by the Chancellor., 1962-1969. (Box 107)
  Index code 190.
- Speeches, Statements, and Articles by Dr. Knudsen., 1960. (Box 107)
  Index code 190K.
- Speeches, Statements, and Articles by Dr. Murphy., 1960. (Box 107)
  Index code 190M.
- Chancellor's Congratulatory Letters., 1969-1970. (Box 108)
  Index code 200.
- Chancellor's Contingent Fund., 1965-1968. (Box 108)
  Index code 197.
- Chancellor's House Maintenance., 1968-1970. (Box 108)
  Index code 198.
- Chancellor's Personal Affairs., 1962-1969. (Box 108)
  Index code 201.
- Dr. Knudsen's Personal., 1960. (Box 108)
- Education and World Affairs (Murphy)., 1968. (Box 108)
  Index code 199.
- Information, Requests for., 1969-1970. (Box 108)
  Index code 216.
- Information. Colleges and University Requests., 1970. (Box 108)
  Index code 216.1.
- Information. Education and Professional Organizations, Government., 1970. (Box 108)
  Index code 216.3.
- Information. Students and Individuals., 1970. (Box 108)
  Index code 216.5.
- Middle East Trip., 1963. (Box 108)
- Miscellaneous Notes., 1960. (Box 108)
- Music Center., 1969. (Box 108)
  Index code 195.
- Public Relations and Information About the University., 1960-1964. (Box 108)
- Questionnaires., 1962-1969. (Box 108)
  Index code 216Q.
- University Cooperation with Government and Private Agencies., 1960-19670. (Box 109)
  Index code 219.
- University-Community Relationships (Planning, Traffic, Parking, Freeways)., 1958-1964.; 1 bound volume (Box 109)
- California and Western Conference Costs and Statistical Study (aka Calif-Big 10 Survey)., 1954-1960.; 1 bound volume (Box 110)
- Gadjah Mada, University of., 1954-1965.; 1 bound volume (Box 110)
- Peace Corps., 1961-1964. (Box 110)
  Index code 219P.
- The Deans Directors, Department Chairman, and Administrative Officers., 1968. (Box 110)
  Index code 220.
- Charter Day., 1960-1965; 1970. (Box 111)
  Index code 221.
- Commencement., 1960-1970. (Box 111)
  Index code 222.
- Honorary Degrees - Shah of Iran., 1964. (Box 111)
  Index code 222-H.
- Honorary Degrees., 1960-1964. (Box 111)
- Mid-Year Graduation Observance., 1943-1961.; 1 bound volume (Box 111)
- Public Ceremonies., 1962-1967; 1967-1970. (Box 111)
  Index code 220.5.
- Public Relations., 1969-1970. (Box 111)
- University Centennial Celebtration. 1968., 1962-1967.; 1 bound volume (Box 111)
- Calendar., 1961-1970. (Box 112)
  Index code 223.
- Quarter System and Year-Round Operations, Conversion to., 1964-1966.; 1 bound volume (Box 112)
- University Meetings and Convocations., 1960-1971. (Box 112)
  Index code 224.
- University Representatives at InAugurations, Meetings, etc., 1960-1966; 1968-1970. (Box 112)
  Index code 226.
- Visitors to Campus., 1963-1970. (Box 112)
  Index code 225.
- University Memberships in Organizations., 1961-1971. (Box 113)
  Filed alphabetically.
  Index code 227.
- Degrees., 1960-1970. (Box 114)
  Index code 232.
- Honorary Degrees., 1962-1970. (Box 114)
  Index code 232-Hon.
- Joint College-Federal Service Council (Federal Executive Development for the Pacific Southwest Region)., 1953-1960.; 1 bound volume (Box 114)
  Index code 227-J.
- Regents' Professors and Lecturers., 1965-1969. (Box 114)
  Index code 231.
- Speakers on Campus., 1961-1970. (Box 114)
  Index code 230.
- Speakers on Campus. Dorothy Healey., 1961-1962.; 1 bound volume (Box 114)
- Subversive Activities and Loyalty Oaths., 1950-1969. (Box 114)
  Index code 228.
- Honorary Degrees. Committee on Honorary Degrees., 1960-1968. (Box 115)
- Honorary Degrees. Individuals., 1965-1968. (Box 115)
- Honorary Degrees. Individuals A-Z., 1965-1969. (Box 115)
- Committee on Honorary Degrees. Exhibit I. (Photograph of Ms. Mary E. Switzer), 1965-1967. (Box 116)
- Committee on Honorary Degrees. Exhibit 2-12. (Selected Publications of Ms. Switzer)., 1965-1967. (Box 116)
- Committee on Honorary Degrees. Exhibit 13-26. (Supporting Letters of M. E. Switzer)., 1965-1967. (Box 116)
- Directories., 1967-1970. (Box 116)
  Index code 234.
- Enrollment., 1967-1970. (Box 116)
  Index code 233.
- Key Sheets. Honorary Degrees., 1961-1966. (Box 116)
- Regents' Matters., 1960-1966. (Box 116)
  Index code 236.
- Regents' Monthly., 1960-1969. (Box 116)
  Index code 237.
- Systems and Procedures, Office of., 1968-1970. (Box 116)
  Index code 235.
- Coordinating Council for Higher Education., 1961-1964. (Box 117)
  Index code 239-C.
- Master Plan for Higher Education in California., 1959-1961. (Box 117)
  Index code 239-L.
- Regents' Committees., 1960. (Box 117)
  Index code 239.
- Regents' Monthly., 1970. (Box 117)
- Regents' Monthly. Committee on Educational Policy., 1970. (Box 117)
  Index code 237.1.
- Regents' Monthly. Sepember 1967. UCLA Campus Presentation. (Box 117)
- Pauley Pavilion., 1960-1969. (Box 118)
  Index code 243.
- President's Advisory Committee on Medical and Health Sciences., 1965. (Box 118)
  Index code 242.
- Student Activities., 1965-1969. (Box 118)
  Index code 245-Act.
- Student Discipline (Including Cheating, Policies and Procedures)., 1965-1967.; 1 bound volume (Box 118)
  Index code 245-Dis.
- Student Discipline., 1965-1969. (Box 118)
- Student Union., 1961-1969. (Box 118)
  Index code 244.
- Students., 1965-1970. (Box 118)
  Index code 245.
- Comments, Complaints., 1965-1970. (Box 119)
  Index code 245.1 [formerly 229].
- Foreign Students., 1965-1970. (Box 119)
  Index code 245-FS.
- International Student Center., 1965-1970. (Box 119)
- Students. Campus Disruptions. Legislation, Federal and State (Including Deny Financial Aid, etc.)., 1969-1970. (Box 119)
  Index code 245.32.
- Students. Campus Disruptions. University and Campus Rules and Procedures for Implementing Anti-Riot Legislation. State and Federal., 1969-1970. (Box 119)
  Index code 245.33.
- Students. Campus Disruptions. Individual Disruptions. May 1970. (Box 119)
  Index code 245.38.
- Students. General. Campus Discipline. Campus Disruptions., 1970. (Box 119)
  Index code 245.3.
- Students. Other U.S. Colleges. Procedures., 1970. (Box 119)
  Index code 245.34.
- Administration and Personnel., 1970. (Box 120)
  Index code 245.95.
- Fellowships. Students., 1970. (Box 120)
  Index code 245.633.
- Financial Aids and Special Services., 1970. (Box 120)
  Index code 245.63.
- Housing Services. Residence Halls., 1970. (Box 120)
  Index code 245.61.
- Housing. Married Students., 1970. (Box 120)
  Index code 245.615.
- Placement and Career Planning., 1970. (Box 120)
  Index code 245.65.
- Residence Halls. Construction., 1970. (Box 120)
- Scholarships., 1970. (Box 120)
  Index code 245.631.
- Student Activities., 1970. (Box 120)
  Index code 245.9.
- Student Legislative Council., 1970. (Box 120)
  Index code 245.951.
- Student Loans., 1970. (Box 120)
  Index code 245.632.
- Student Participation in Governance., 1969-1970. (Box 120)
  Index code 245.5.
- Student Participation in Political Elections., 1970. (Box 120)
  Index code 245.6.
- Student Services and Dean of Students., 1970. (Box 120)
- Students. Campus Disruptions. Individual Disruptions. May 1970. Letters from UC Personnel. Faculty, Staff, Students, Regents. (Box 120)
- Students. Campus Disruptions. Individual Disruptions. May 1970. May 5 and 6. Police (Including Chancellor's Commission on the Events of May 5, 1970). (Box 120)
- Students. Campus Disruptions. Individual Disruptions. June 7 ROTC., 1970. (Box 120)
- Students. Campus Disruptions. Individual Disruptions. Report on Academic Programs at UCLA, etc., 1970. (Box 120)
- Work Study., 1970. (Box 120)
  Index code 245.634.
- ASUCLA., 1960-1964. (Box 121)
  Index code 246.
- Board of Communications. Bruin, Press, KLA., 1970. (Box 121)
  Index code 245.953.
- Board of Control., 1960-1970. (Box 121)
  Index code 245.952.
- Committee on Campus Press (Includes Final Report)., 1970. (Box 121)
  Index code 245.93.
- Community Service., 1967-1970. (Box 121)
  Index code 245.955.
- Special Commission on Student Press., 1970. (Box 121)
- Student Facilities., 1970. (Box 121)
  Index code 245.958.
- Students. Board of Communications. Daily Bruin Issue 1970 may 27. (Box 121)
- Students. Graduate Student Association., 1970. (Box 121)
  Index code 245.96.
- ASUCLA Constitution., 1950-1958.; 1 bound volume (Box 122)
- ASUCLA., 1965-1969. (Box 122)
- Food Stands., 1947-1959.; 1 bound volume (Box 122)
  Index code 246-B.
- Freedom Riders., 1961-1962. (Box 122)
- Student Government. Kerr Directives., 1958-1964.; 1 bound volume (Box 122)
- Vending Machines., 1945-1963. (Box 122)
- Archaeology, Institute of., 1968-1969. (Box 123)
  Index code 249.
- Bank in the Student Union., 1957-1963.; 1 bound volume (Box 123)
  Index code 246-StU.
- Daily Bruin., 1956-1969. (Box 123)
  Index code 246-DB.
- Forms., 1966-1967. (Box 123)
  Index code 248.
- Intercollegiate Athletic Advisory Council., 1959-1960.; 1 bound volume (Box 123)
  Index code 246-S.
- Selective Service., 1968-1970. (Box 123)
  Index code 250.
- Student Union Fees., 1957-1960.; 1 bound volume (Box 123)
  Index code 246-StUFees.
- Transfer of Administrative Control of Athletics from Associated Students to the Administration., 1959-1960.; 1 bound volume (Box 123)
- Faculty Development Program. UCLA., 1968-1970. (Box 124)
  Index code 252.
- Individual UCLA Faculty Response to University's Role in the Urban Crisis., 1968.; 1 bound volume (Box 124)
  Index code 251.
- Reports. UCLA's Response to Urban Crisis., 1967-1969. (Box 124)
  Index code 253.
- Reports. UCLA's Response to Urban Crisis., 1967-1969. (Box 124)
- Urban Crisis. Universitywide., 1968-1970. (Box 124)
- Urban Research (BURD, Pico-Union, Compton) at UCLA., 1967-1970. (Box 124)
- BURD Requested Financial Support., 1968. (Box 125)
- General, SEP, TOP, SWOP (Summer Work Opportunity Program)., 1970. (Box 125)
  Index code 254.
- High Potential Program., 1969-1970. (Box 125)
- Special Education Programs., 1968-1969. (Box 125)
- Task Force Reports. Summer 1968. (Box 125)
- UCLA MECHA., 1970. (Box 125)
- Homecoming, All University functions, Cal Club., 1960-1969. (Box 126)
  Index code 256.
- Minority non-academic personnel., 1969-1970. (Box 126)
  Index code 257.
- Office of Publications., 1963-1968. (Box 126)
  Index code 261.
- Publications from Faculty and Staff., 1969-1970. (Box 126)
  Index code 262.
- Publications from Others., 1969. (Box 126)
  Index code 263.
- University [of California] Press., 1960-1962. (Box 126)
- University Bulletins., 1969. (Box 126)
  Index code 266.
- Afro-American cultural program/studies center., 1968-1969. (Box 127)
  Index code 255.
- American Indian Studies Center., 1969-1970. (Box 127)
- Asian American Studies Center., 1969-1970. (Box 127)
- Ethnic programs and centers., 1968-1970. (Box 127)
- Institute of American Cultures., 1968-1969. (Box 127)
- Mexican American study/cultural center., 1969-1970. (Box 127)
- Closing of Westwood Blvd., 1958-1961. (Box 128, Folder 1)
  Index: 219/18.
- Regulation 17 - distribution of unauthorized literature., 1947-1963. (Box 128, Folder 2)
  Index: 106.
- No title., 1960-1969. (Box 128, Folder 3)
  Index 105.
- Department reviews., 1968. (Box 128, Folder 4-9)
- Department reviews., 1967-1968. (Box 129, Folder 1-7)
- Teaching Assistants., 1965. (Box 129, Folder 8)
- Ford Foundation., 1967-1970. (Box 130, Folder 1-3)
- Decentralization., 1969-1970. (Box 130, Folder 4)
- Department reviews., 1966-1967. (Box 130, Folder 5)
- American Cultures Project and Ethnic Centers., 1969. (Box 130, Folder 6-8)
- Department of Economics., 1966-1967. (Box 130, Folder 9)
- HENAC - Humanistic & Educational Needs of the Academic Community. Ford Foundation., 1970. (Box 131, Folder 1)
- Ford Foundation., 1970. (Box 131, Folder 2)
- Ford Foundation grant application for HENAC., 1970. (Box 131, Folder 3)
- Chancellors Planning Committee., 1959. (Box 131, Folder 4)
- Orders of the President., 1954. (Box 131, Folder 5)
- Committee on Fees., 1941-1948. (Box 131, Folder 6)
- Chancellor's Administrative Council - minutes., 1958. (Box 132, Folder 1)
- Chancellor's Planning Committee., 1960 Feb-Mar. (Box 132, Folder 2)
- Chancellor's Planning Committee., 1958. (Box 132, Folder 3)
- Chancellor's Planning Committee - listed by schools., 1958-1960. (Box 132, Folder 4)
- Chancellor's Advisory Council., 1959-1960. (Box 132, Folder 5-6)
- Chancellor's Administrative Council - minutes., 1956-1957. (Box 132, Folder 7-8)
- Chancellor's Administrative Council - minutes., 1958-1959. (Box 133, Folder 1)
- Informal Administrative Conference., 1948-1955. (Box 133, Folder 2)
- UC President's Office - Manual of Procedure., 1948. (Box 133, Folder 3)
- Music - Lachman Collection of Historical Stringed Instruments., 1951-1965. (Box 133, Folder 4)
- An Evaluation of Campus Recreation at UCLA, January 1955 (Box 134)
- Report on Sub-committee on Appointment of a Provost at UCLA, October 1950 (Box 134)
- Report, Law School Planning Committee, Los Angeles, October, 1947 (Box 134)
- Chancellor's Planning Committee, 1957 (Box 134)
- Anti-Vietnam demonstrations at UC Berkeley and UCLA including the Occupation of Murphy Hall and charges against Gordon Alexander, 1969 (Box 134)
- Statement Regarding Teaching, Research and Service in Nutritions; Space Requirements and Assignments, 1960 (Box 134)
- Advisory Committee on the Use of the Incidental Fee Income, 1965-1969; 2 folders (Box 134)